ccopy_reg
_reconstructor
p1
(cfeedparser
FeedParserDict
p2
c__builtin__
dict
p3
(dp4
S'feed'
p5
g1
(g2
g3
(dp6
S'updated'
p7
VNo date found.
p8
sS'updated_parsed'
p9
NsS'links'
p10
(lp11
g1
(g2
g3
(dp12
S'href'
p13
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p14
sS'type'
p15
Vapplication/atom+xml
p16
sS'rel'
p17
Vself
p18
stRp19
ag1
(g2
g3
(dp20
S'href'
p21
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com
p22
sg15
Vtext/html
p23
sS'rel'
p24
Valternate
p25
stRp26
asS'title'
p27
VWhat If?
p28
sS'author'
p29
Vxkcd (whatif@xkcd.com)
p30
sS'guidislink'
p31
I00
sS'title_detail'
p32
g1
(g2
g3
(dp33
S'base'
p34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p35
sg15
Vtext/plain
p36
sS'language'
p37
NsS'value'
p38
g28
stRp39
sS'link'
p40
g22
sS'authors'
p41
(lp42
g1
(g2
g3
(dp43
S'name'
p44
Vxkcd
p45
sS'email'
p46
Vwhatif@xkcd.com
p47
stRp48
asS'author_detail'
p49
g1
(g2
g3
(dp50
g44
g45
sg46
g47
stRp51
sS'id'
p52
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p53
stRp54
sS'status'
p55
I200
sg7
S'Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:42:50 GMT'
p56
sg9
ctime
struct_time
p57
((I2013
I3
I19
I16
I42
I50
I1
I78
I0
t(dtRp58
sS'encoding'
p59
Vutf-8
p60
sS'bozo'
p61
I0
sS'entries'
p62
(lp63
g1
(g2
g3
(dp64
S'summary_detail'
p65
g1
(g2
g3
(dp66
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p67
sg15
Vtext/html
p68
sg37
Nsg38
V<article class="entry">\u000a  <a href="http://what-if.xkcd.com/37/"><h1>Supersonic Stereo</h1></a>\u000a  <p id="question">What if you somehow managed to make a stereo travel at twice the speed of sound, would it sound backwards to someone who was just casually sitting somewhere as it flies by?</p>\u000a\u000a<p id="attribute">\u2014Tim Currie</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Yes.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Technically, anyway. It would be pretty hard to hear.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>The basic idea is pretty straightforward. The stereo is going faster than its own sound, so it will reach you first, followed by the sound it emitted one second ago, followed by the sound it emitted two seconds ago, and so forth.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/37/stereo_waves.png" title="the cone defined by the edge of the run-together overlapping circles is the shockwave that makes a sonic boom as it sweeps along the ground" />\u000a\u000a<p>The problem is that the stereo is moving at Mach 2, which means that two seconds ago, it was over a kilometer away. It\u2019s hard to hear music from that distance, particularly when your ears were just hit by (a) a sonic boom, and (b) pieces of a rapidly disintegrating stereo.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Wind speeds of Mach 2 would messily disassemble most consumer electronics. The force of the wind on the body of the stereo is roughly comparable to that of a dozen people standing on it:</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/37/stereo_standing.png" title="this is the vibe that most of my parties have" />\u000a\u000a<p>An ordinary stereo wouldn\u2019t make it, but one with some kind of ruggedized high-strength casing might be able to survive.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>If we put together a durable, heavy-duty stereo and launch it on a ballistic trajectory, it will only be traveling at supersonic speeds for the first 150 meters or so. This means that the target will hear a maximum of about a third of a second of reversed music.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>This phenomenon is actually confirmed in the 2008 paper <em><a href="http://www.researchgate.net/publication/230702229_Reproduction_of_Virtual_Sound_Sources_Moving_at_Supersonic_Speeds_in_Wave_Field_Synthesis">Reproduction of Virtual Sound Sources Moving at Supersonic Speeds in Wave Field Synthesis</a></em>, which says that the sound wave field \u201ccontains a component carrying a time-reversed version of the source\u2019s input signal\u201d. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>The sonic boom would be the first thing the target would hear. It would be followed by several sounds played over one another, including both reversed music (rising slightly in pitch as it fades out) and forward-playing music (which would play at half speed and an octave too low), followed by the crash of a stereo demolishing your neighbor\u2019s shed.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Which means that if you\u2019re playing one of those albums containing secret demonic messages, the result will be the strangest listening experience of your life:</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/37/stereo_message.png" title="my cabbages!" />\u000a\u000a</article>
p69
stRp70
sg10
(lp71
g1
(g2
g3
(dp72
S'href'
p73
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/37/
p74
sg15
g23
sg24
g25
stRp75
asS'published_parsed'
p76
Nsg27
VSupersonic Stereo
p77
sg7
VNo date found.
p78
sS'summary'
p79
g69
sg31
I00
sS'title_detail'
p80
g1
(g2
g3
(dp81
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p82
sg15
g36
sg37
Nsg38
g77
stRp83
sg40
g74
sS'published'
p84
VNo date found.
p85
sS'canto_state'
p86
(lp87
VWhat If?
p88
aV*
aS'read'
p89
asg52
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/37/
p90
sg9
NstRp91
ag1
(g2
g3
(dp92
S'summary_detail'
p93
g1
(g2
g3
(dp94
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p95
sg15
g68
sg37
Nsg38
V<article class="entry">\u000a  <a href="http://what-if.xkcd.com/36/"><h1>Cornstarch</h1></a>\u000a  <p id="question">How much cornstarch can I rinse down the drain before unpleasant things start to happen?</p>\u000a\u000a<p id="attribute">\u2014Anna R., Fort Wayne, IN</p>\u000a\u000a<p>It depends what you consider unpleasant.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>If you watered down the cornstarch enough, you could likely pour it down the drain for years without any ill effects. If it didn\u2019t clog the sink, the rest of the pipes could probably handle it. It might provoke some confusion among the sewage treatment people, but it wouldn\u2019t break anything. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>But it\u2019d be terrifically boring (and thus unpleasant) to pour cornstarch down a sink all day, so I guess that\u2019s\u2014</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_boring.png" title="the questioner pours cornstarch into a drain" />\u000a\u000a<p>\u2026 Oh. Huh. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>Well, let\u2019s thicken the cornstarch.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>When you mix cornstarch and water in a bit under a 2:1 ratio, you get oobleck, a substance with some odd physical properties. This is a great kitchen science experiment everyone should try at least once.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>At low speeds, oobleck behaves like a liquid. If you gently swish your fingers in a bowl of it, it feels like milk or heavy cream. However, if you make a fist and punch the surface, your hand bounces off with a thud\u2014it\u2019s like hitting a slab of raw meat. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>If you vibrate oobleck, even <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3zoTKXXNQIU">stranger things happen</a>.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>It wouldn\u2019t take much of the mixture to clog a drain. It depends on your plumbing, but you could probably stop up your sink with a small bowl of it. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>Since your drain is clogged, I guess that\u2019s the answer to your question.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_clogged.png" title="the drain is clogged but it's ok" />\u000a\u000a<p>Well, ok. I guess some people don\u2019t mind clogged drains.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>If you keep at it, after a few minutes, your sink will overflow, spilling goop onto your floor.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_floor.png" title="let the cornstarch hit the floor" />\u000a\u000a<p>Financially, this will be hard to keep up. If you\u2019re mixing as fast as the water will come out of the sink, this project may cost you in the neighborhood of $5,000 per day if you can\u2019t find a good bulk distributor.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_bitcoins.png" title="by the time you read this, bitcoins will be either hilariously expensive or hilariously cheap" />\u000a\u000a<p>At this rate, it should build up on the floor at a rate of an inch or two per day.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_fun.png" title="pouring cornstarch into the sink is endless fun" />\u000a\u000a<p>If your doors are sealed well, it will continue to build up. Once it reaches knee height (a week or two after you started), you may be able to hold the rising tide at bay for a little bit\u2014at least in one room\u2014by getting someone to flush the toilet repeatedly. The pipes there are larger and harder to clog; the limiting factor would probably be how fast the tank filled with water.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_toilet.png" title="this is probably a violation of your lease" />\u000a\u000a<p>Eventually, after a month or two, the oobleck would reach the living room window. The pressure would quickly rise, and sooner or later the window would burst.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>As the deadly <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boston_Molasses_Disaster">Boston Molasses Flood</a> proved, even thick, viscous fluids can flow quickly when in large enough quantities. The oobleck would pour rapidly out onto the lawn, carrying you with it.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>At this point, the local officials would probably notice and, at the very least, shut off your water.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/36/cornstarch_lawn.png" title="be careful of the broken glass while you're being swept out through the window" />\u000a\u000a<p>But I guess if you really like cornstarch that much, nothing unpleasant has happened.</p>\u000a\u000a</article>
p96
stRp97
sg10
(lp98
g1
(g2
g3
(dp99
S'href'
p100
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/36/
p101
sg15
g23
sg24
g25
stRp102
asg76
g57
((I2013
I3
I12
I0
I0
I0
I1
I71
I0
t(dtRp103
sg27
VCornstarch
p104
sg7
V2013-03-12T00:00:00Z
p105
sg79
g96
sg31
I00
sS'title_detail'
p106
g1
(g2
g3
(dp107
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p108
sg15
g36
sg37
Nsg38
g104
stRp109
sg40
g101
sg84
V2013-03-12T00:00:00Z
p110
sg86
(lp111
g88
aV*
ag89
asg52
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/36/
p112
sg9
g57
((I2013
I3
I12
I0
I0
I0
I1
I71
I0
t(dtRp113
stRp114
ag1
(g2
g3
(dp115
S'summary_detail'
p116
g1
(g2
g3
(dp117
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p118
sg15
g68
sg37
Nsg38
V<article class="entry">\u000a  <a href="http://what-if.xkcd.com/35/"><h1>Hair Dryer</h1></a>\u000a  <p id="question">What would happen if a hair dryer with continuous power was turned on and put in an airtight 1x1x1 meter box?</p>\u000a\u000a<p id="attribute">\u2014Dry Paratroopa</p>\u000a\u000a<p>A typical hair dryer draws 1875 watts of power.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>All 1875 watts have to go somewhere. No matter what happens inside the box, if there\u2019s 1875 watts of power being used, eventually there will be 1875 watts of heat flowing out.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>This is true of any device that uses power, which is a handy thing to know. For example, people worry about leaving disconnected chargers plugged into the wall for fear that they\u2019re draining power. Are they right? You can use heat flow to come up with simple rule of thumb: If an unused charger isn\u2019t warm to the touch, it\u2019s using less than a penny of electricity a day. For a small smartphone charger, if it\u2019s not warm to the touch, it\u2019s using less than a penny a <em>year</em>. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>This is true of almost any powered device (though not necessarily those plugged into a second device. If a charger is connected to something, like a smartphone or laptop, power can be flowing from the wall through the charger into the device.)</p>\u000a\u000a<p>But back to the box.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Heat will flow from the hair dryer out into the box. If we assume the dryer is indestructible, the interior of the box will keep getting hotter until the outer surface reaches about 60°C (140°F). At that temperature, the box will be losing heat to the outside as fast as the hair dryer is adding it inside, and the system will be in equilibrium. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_equilibrium.png" title="it's warmer than my parents! it's my new parents." />\u000a\u000a<p class="aside">The equilibrium temperature will be a bit cooler if there\u2019s a breeze, or if the box is sitting on a wet or metallic surface that conducts away heat quickly.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>If the box is made of metal, 60°C is hot enough to <a href="http://www.mascoat.com/assets/files/Insulative_Coating_Evaluation_NACE.pdf">burn your hand if you touch it</a> for more than five seconds. If it\u2019s wood, you can probably touch it for a while, but there\u2019s a danger that parts of the box in contact with the mouth of the hair dryer will catch fire.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>The inside of a box will be like an oven. The temperature it reaches will depend on the thickness of the box wall; the thicker and more insulating the wall, the higher the temperature. It wouldn\u2019t take a very thick box to create temperatures high enough to burn out the hair dryer. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>But let\u2019s assume an indestructible hair dryer. And if we have something as cool as an indestructible hair dryer, it seems like a shame to limit it.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_18750.png" title="anything is possible with tape" />\u000a\u000a<p>With 18,750 watts flowing out of the hair dryer, the surface of the box reaches over 200°C (475°F), as hot as a skillet on low-medium.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_breakfast.png" title="new momdad is great!" />\u000a\u000a<p>I wonder how high this dial goes.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_187500.png" title="there's a distresing amount of space left on the dial" />\u000a\u000a<p>The surface of the box is now 600°C, hot enough to glow a dim red.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_box600.png" title="the box is glowing" />\u000a\u000a<p>If it\u2019s made of aluminium, the inside is starting to melt. If it\u2019s made of lead, the outside is starting to melt. If it\u2019s on a wood floor, the house is on fire. But it doesn't matter what's happening around it; the hair dryer is indestructible.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1875000.png" title="the box is glowing more" />\u000a\u000a<p>Two megawatts <a href="http://what-if.xkcd.com/13/">pumped into a laser</a> is enough to destroy missiles. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>At 1300°C, the box is now about the temperature of lava.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_box1500.png" title="the box is looking melty" />\u000a\u000a<p>One more notch.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_18750000.png" title="this hair dryer is probably not up to code" />\u000a\u000a<p>18 megawatts are flowing into the box. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_box2400.png" title="the box exudes a pleasant yellow glow" />\u000a\u000a<p>The surface of the box reaches 2400°C. If it were steel, it would have melted by now. If it\u2019s made of something like tungsten, it might conceivably last a little longer.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Just one more, then we'll stop.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_187500000.png" title="the hair dryer is turned to 187 megawatts, somehow" />\u000a\u000a<p>187 megawatts is enough to make the box glow white. Not a lot of box materials can survive these conditions, so we\u2019ll have to assume the box is indestructible. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_box4500.png" title="the floor is made of lava" />\u000a\u000a<p>Unfortunately, the floor isn\u2019t. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>Before it can burn its way through the floor, someone throws a water balloon under it. The burst of steam launches the box out the front door and onto the sidewalk. (Note: If you\u2019re ever trapped with me in a burning building, and I suggest an idea for how we could escape the situation, it\u2019s probably best to ignore me.)</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1875000000.png" title="settings are added with reckless abandon" />\u000a\u000a<p>1.875 gigawatts (I lied about stopping). According to <em>Back to the Future</em>, the hair dryer is now drawing enough power to travel back in time.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_box8000.png" title="a tiny star sits in a pool of fire" />\u000a\u000a<p>The box is blindingly bright, and you can\u2019t get closer than a few hundred meters due to the intense heat. It sits in the middle of a growing pool of lava. Anything within 50-100 meters bursts into flame. A column of heat and smoke rise high into the air. Periodic explosions of gas beneath the box launch it into the air, and it starts fires and forms a new lava pool where it lands. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_18750000000.png" title="more settings are added via some impressively durable tape" />\u000a\u000a<p>18.7 gigawatts. The conditions around the box are similar to those on the pad during a Space Shuttle launch. The box begins to be tossed around by the powerful updrafts it\u2019s creating.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>In 1914, H.G. Wells imagined devices like this in his book <em><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_World_Set_Free">The World Set Free</a></em>. He wrote of a type of bomb that, instead of exploding once, exploded <em>continuously</em>, a slow-burn inferno that started inextinguishable fires in the hearts of cities. The story eerily foreshadowed the development, 30 years later, of nuclear weapons.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1e11.png" title="hair dryers left plugged in have been known to start fires, but rarely so enthusiastically as this one" />\u000a\u000a<p>The box is now soaring through the air. Each time it nears the ground, it superheats the surface, and the plume of expanding air hurls it back into the sky.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1e12.png" title="the un has expressed concern that rogue states may gain access to hair dryer power dial labeling technology" />\u000a\u000a<p>1.875 terawatts is like a house-sized stack of TNT going off <em>every second</em>. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1e13.png" title="we're running out of space, fortunately" />\u000a\u000a<p>A trail of firestorms\u2014massive conflagrations which sustain themselves by creating their own wind systems\u2014winds its way across the landscape.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>A new milestone: The hair dryer is now, impossibly, consuming more power than every other electrical device on the planet combined.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1e14.png" title="that's the last one, right?" />\u000a\u000a<p>The box, soaring high above the surface, is putting out energy equivalent to three Trinity tests every <em>second</em>. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>At this point, the pattern is obvious. This thing is going to skip around the atmosphere until it destroys the planet. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>Let's try something different.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_0.png" title="the dial is turned back to zero" />\u000a\u000a<p>We turn the dial to zero as the box is passing over northern Canada. Rapidly cooling, it plummets to Earth, landing in Great Bear Lake with a plume of steam. And then \u2026</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_1e16.png" title="every dial goes to 11 if you turn it hard enough" />\u000a\u000a<p class="aside">This one goes to 11. Petawatts, in this case.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>A brief story:</p>\u000a\u000a<p>The official record for fastest manmade object is the Helios 2 probe, which reached about 70 km/s in a close swing around the Sun. But it\u2019s possible the actual holder of that title is a two-ton metal manhole cover. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>The cover sat atop a shaft at an underground nuclear test site operated by Los Alamos as part of Operation Plumbbob. When the one-kiloton nuke went off below, the facility effectively became a <a href="http://nfttu.blogspot.com/2006/01/nuclear-potato-cannon-part-2.html">nuclear potato cannon</a>, giving the cap a gigantic kick. A high-speed camera trained on the lid caught only one frame of it moving upward before it vanished\u2014which means it was moving at a minimum of 66 km/s. The cap was never found.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>66 km/s is about six times escape velocity, but contrary to the linked blog\u2019s speculation, it\u2019s unlikely the cap ever reached space. <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Impact_depth">Newton\u2019s impact depth approximation</a> suggests that it was either destroyed completely by impact with the air or slowed and fell back to Earth.</p>\u000a\u000a<p>Our suddenly-activated hair dryer box, bobbing in lake water, undergoes a similar process. The heated steam below it expands outward, and as the box rises into the air, the entire surface of the lake turns to steam. The steam, heated to a plasma by the flood of radiation, accelerates the box faster and faster. </p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_launch.png" title="photo courtesy cmdr. hadfield" />\u000a\u000a<p>Rather than slam into the atmosphere like the manhole cover, the flood of radiation heats the air around it, creating a bubble of expanding plasma which offers little resistance. The box exits the atmosphere and continues away, slowly fading from second sun to dim star. Much of the Northwest Territories is burning, but the Earth has survived. </p>\u000a\u000a<p>Although we may wish we hadn't.</p>\u000a\u000a<img class="illustration" src="http://what-if.xkcd.com/imgs/a/35/hair_dryer_bill.png" title="the bill is about $20 trillion, give or take" />\u000a\u000a</article>
p119
stRp120
sg10
(lp121
g1
(g2
g3
(dp122
S'href'
p123
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/35/
p124
sg15
g23
sg24
g25
stRp125
asg76
g57
((I2013
I3
I5
I0
I0
I0
I1
I64
I0
t(dtRp126
sg27
VHair Dryer
p127
sg7
V2013-03-05T00:00:00Z
p128
sg79
g119
sg31
I00
sS'title_detail'
p129
g1
(g2
g3
(dp130
g34
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p131
sg15
g36
sg37
Nsg38
g127
stRp132
sg40
g124
sg84
V2013-03-05T00:00:00Z
p133
sg86
(lp134
g88
aV*
ag89
asg52
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/35/
p135
sg9
g57
((I2013
I3
I5
I0
I0
I0
I1
I64
I0
t(dtRp136
stRp137
asS'canto_update'
p138
F1364190768.125767
sS'headers'
p139
(dp140
S'content-length'
p141
S'19680'
p142
sS'accept-ranges'
p143
S'bytes'
p144
sS'expires'
p145
S'Mon, 25 Mar 2013 06:02:34 GMT'
p146
sS'server'
p147
S'lighttpd/1.4.28'
p148
sS'last-modified'
p149
g56
sS'connection'
p150
S'close'
p151
sS'etag'
p152
S'"1378548602"'
p153
sS'cache-control'
p154
S'max-age=600'
p155
sS'date'
p156
S'Mon, 25 Mar 2013 05:52:34 GMT'
p157
sS'content-type'
p158
S'application/atom+xml; charset=utf-8'
p159
ssS'etag'
p160
V"1378548602"
p161
sg86
(lp162
sS'href'
p163
Vhttp://what-if.xkcd.com/feed.atom
p164
sS'version'
p165
Vatom10
p166
sS'canto_version'
p167
(I0
I7
I10
tp168
sS'namespaces'
p169
(dp170
S''
Vhttp://www.w3.org/2005/Atom
p171
sstRp172
.